Το Plex ζήτησε 120€ για να συνεχίσετε να βλέπετε από τις συσκευές σας.
Το πλήρωσα εγώ το ποσό.
Αν χρησιμοποιείτε συχνά και μπορείτε,
οποιαδήποτε συμβολή θα εκτιμηθεί.
Flamme.
You mean "Master."
What is it?
Do you really think it's unfair?
Frieren, do you remember Basalt's last words?
No.
Their kind uses words only to deceive humans.
That's right.
They're nothing more than monsters
capable of speech.
That's the true nature of the
creatures I call demons.
They don't play fair,
so we must be even more unfair.
If it allows me to exterminate demonkind,
then I will gladly embrace this dishonor.
Like a fairy tale
It's a sign the story has reached its end
Like a single passage taken from
A journey that was too long
Of the evil that once cast a shadow
Across this land
And the memories of the short journey
With the hero who defeated it
The story ends
And the hero goes to sleep
Leaving this land with
Days of peace and quiet
The passage of time heartlessly
Makes people forget
Even the tracks left behind by his life
Begin to rust
Just the same
Your words and wishes and courage
Are still inside of me
And they live on
We chose the same path
That's all it was supposed to be
Why is it that at some point
I wanted to understand the reason for
The tears that fall down my cheeks
Even now
If I retrace the journey we walked together
Even though you're not there
I know I'll be able to find it
The bleeding won't stop.
This is the end.
Your plan has failed.
You're right.
But Frieren won't escape unscathed.
She must be fighting Lady Aura by now.
Previously, we were forced to
retreat by the party of heroes.
But this time, there are
no heroes to protect her.
It's true that Frieren is a threat to us,
but she has far less mana than Lady Aura.
If she engages her directly,
Frieren will lose.
Then Frieren will win.
She'd never directly engage a demon.
I know she'll trick Aura and kill her.
Nonsense.
Frieren the Slayer has always
engaged us directly.
Why do I feel like something is wrong?
This girl's mana is weak,
and yet I was overwhelmed by the
sheer number of her rapid attacks.
But how was she able to do that
without exhausting her mana?
I understand now. Is that even possible?
So Frieren does the same.
What you've done isn't fair.
You're a disgrace to all mages.
Ms. Frieren knows that better than anyone.
What a dreadful sight.
Looks like an elf village.
Basalt the Throne,
a general of the Demon King's army.
He must've led his forces here
to destroy this village.
Are you the one who killed him?
You seem nearly dead yourself.
That's a lot of mana.
You must be powerful.
Did you engage the demons directly?
What a fool you are.
Why do people always engage
their enemies directly?
Run, hide, take your enemies by surprise...
There are plenty of other options.
I'll never understand strong mages.
But you do.
What?
You should understand how I feel...
because you're a far more powerful mage.
What makes you say that?
Just a feeling.
What's your name?
What happened to the village?
Its people are dead, down to
the last woman and child.
I was the strongest, but I still
couldn't protect them.
You really are a fool.
If I'd been in your shoes,
I wouldn't have hesitated to run.
Put me down.
No.
You have potential.
You're going to be my apprentice.
And you know you wouldn't have survived
if I hadn't happened upon you.
On top of failing to protect the village,
you nearly died yourself.
Your death truly would've been in vain.
We're being pursued.
They're stronger than the general you killed.
Interesting creatures, aren't they?
They had every intention
of catching us off guard
by concealing their mana
until just before they struck,
but the moment they realized we were mages,
they stepped out into the open.
They're cunning and they don't play fair,
but every last one of them has a ridiculous
sense of pride when it comes to magic.
Human mage, leave the elf girl and go.
Will you let me go if I do?
"Kill all the elves."
Those were the Demon King's orders.
Your life matters not to me.
I see.
Frieren, it's true that I'm painfully aware
of what it's like to be a powerful mage.
I know exactly how these creatures feel, too.
I know the absolute confidence they
have in the magics they've studied.
In other words, they're stupidly
proud and overconfident.
Frieren, unlike you,
they judged me a weakling.
Though they were exceptional mages,
their overconfidence cost them their lives.
You hid your strength by controlling
how much mana you release.
That's right.
Deceive and kill your enemies by allowing
them to miscalculate your strength.
It's a cowardly and unfair way to fight
that makes a mockery of magic.
Your injuries are looking a lot better.
Shall we begin your training?
Flamme.
You mean "Master."
Demons took everything from me.
Me, too.
I hate them so much that I wish
I could exterminate every last one.
Me, too.
But I love magic.
So do I.
Which is why only you and I should become
cowards who make a mockery of magic.
What should I do to train?
Try limiting the mana you release
to one-tenth of its normal volume.
Impressive. You're controlling it well.
Any elf can do this.
While you do that, we'll work on your
fundamentals and raise your base mana level.
That's all?
Simple, right?
By the way, how long should
I keep suppressing my mana?
It starts to get tiring
if I do it for too long.
As long as I do.
For life.
You'll spend your entire life fooling demons.
Lügner is dead.
Now all your executioners
have been eliminated.
You've failed, Aura.
You're right. It's a shame.
But if I can defeat you here,
then it won't have been for nothing.
In this battle, you've released numerous
immortal soldiers from my control.
Was it wise to expend so much mana against me?
The Scales of Obedience.
When two souls are placed on the scale,
whichever has more mana
forces the other to submit.
Aura can only use such a risky spell
because of her tremendous amount of mana.
Generally speaking,
a person's mana increases in proportion
with the time spent training.
I can feel it in the mana pouring off Aura.
She's a great demon who has lived
for over five hundred years,
and she's spent most of her life training.
Five hundred years, huh?
That's fairly long-lived for a demon.
I doubt she's been challenged before.
I can learn so much just from
the mana flowing off her.
Regardless, demons don't conceal
their mana—nor can they.
A pity.
Auserlese.
Master.
Demons are cunning, aren't they?
Why don't they constantly suppress
their mana like you do?
They can't.
Demons are individualists,
but they form the barest connections
needed to fight against humankind.
What do you think an organization
needs to function?
Order?
That's right.
In other words, you need someone
important to lead an organization.
In the case of humans,
importance is determined by status
and wealth, like they do in this nation.
That well-dressed man exiting
that palace is a man of importance.
It's hard to tell which humans are important,
so they dress themselves up
to make it obvious.
Demons are different?
They haven't changed a bit
since they were monsters.
Might makes right.
It's far easier to understand than humans.
You can tell who's strong
just by looking at them.
You mean mana.
Mana is to them what status
and wealth are for humans.
It's dignity itself.
They may temporarily suppress
their mana for the sake of stealth,
but none are foolish enough
to suppress their mana all the time.
It's the difference between a noble
sneaking out into town incognito
and that same noble debasing themselves by
abandoning their status and wealth entirely.
The world of demons is cruel.
They'd never grant any dignity
to those with little mana.
So the stronger they are, the more desperate
they are to show off their mana.
For them, there's no benefit to
constantly suppressing their mana.
It doesn't even occur to them to do it.
It's a pity, isn't it?
Just as humans are bound by status
and wealth, demons are bound by mana.
Despite their pride in
and unparalleled love for magic,
they can't control their own mana.
Frieren, you're lucky you're not a demon.
You're right. I wouldn't be able
to deceive them if I were.
It's been three years since you
started suppressing your mana.
Looks like I was right about you.
You've grown much better at that.
Frieren, do you still love magic?
Where did that come from, Master?
Somewhat, I suppose.
Long ago, you once confidently
answered that you loved magic.
That was only fifty years ago.
You're right.
In the end, all I could do
was teach you to fight.
Magic for revenge.
Do you regret it?
No. I'm glad I taught my magic to you.
Given how long you'll live,
you might eventually become strong
enough to defeat the Demon King.
Frieren, I have one request.
What is it?
Plant flowers around my grave.
That doesn't seem like you.
I know.
Frieren, my favorite spell
creates a field of beautiful flowers.
My parents taught it to me when I was little.
It's what made me love magic.
Huh.
Teach me that spell.
Listen to me, Frieren.
You must never seek to leave
your name in history.
Live in obscurity.
You won't leave your name in history
until you defeat the Demon King.
I've heard there's a long-lived
mage in these woods.
Are you her?
I've lived a long time, but I haven't
done much with my life.
I'm not exceptional.
Huh. What do you think, Heiter?
She has roughly one-fifth of my mana.
It's not bad.
Who's this irritating guy?
Leave. You don't have business
with a mediocre mage, do you?
No, you're stronger than
any mage I've ever met.
What makes you say that?
Just a feeling.
Auserlese.
You seem happy, Aura.
Are you certain you'll win?
You'll see.
Frieren the Slayer.
You made your first major
appearance eighty years ago.
With the party of heroes,
you defeated the Demon King.
You're a mysterious elven mage
whose age is unknown.
But it doesn't matter how
long-lived a mage you are.
Your mana tells me everything
I need to know.
I can see it quite clearly.
You're an exceptional mage,
but your mana itself is unimpressive.
You can't have had more than a
hundred years or so of training.
Not only that, but you've barely
changed since eighty years ago.
Were you honing other skills
instead of working on your mana?
Or were you simply wasting your life away?
Either way, you are no match for me.
I win.
All that's left is to sever your head myself.
It wasn't even necessary
to exhaust Frieren's mana.
I needn't have been so cautious.
She defeated many of my
immortal soldiers, too.
I'll have to replenish their numbers later.
What's this?
The scales are starting to tip toward Frieren.
You placed my soul on the scales, Aura.
Honestly, I would've been in trouble
if you'd tried to overwhelm me with numbers.
I'm glad you're so confident in your own mana.
Now I can finally defeat you.
What do you mean?
You should've figured it out by now.
I've been suppressing my mana.
You misjudged the situation, Aura.
That's impossible. That wouldn't
have escaped my notice.
There was no hint of the instability
or variation in mana output
that comes with suppression.
I'm surprised. Demons are capable
of observing mana that precisely?
Sounds like my master made the
right call with her methods.
I've spent most of my life
suppressing my mana.
This state has become natural for me.
Are you stupid? Why would you
do something so pointless?
You're right. It's stupid.
But it lets me beat your kind.
This is absurd.
I'm a great demon who's lived
for over five hundred years.
Aura, the person standing before you...
is a mage who's lived
for over a thousand years.
Frieren.
Just as demons deceive humankind with words,
you must use your mana to deceive demons.
Aura,
kill yourself.
Impossible.
H-How could I...?
And you alright
Can you hear me
Trailing along deserted train tracks
Crying excessively
Wanting you to smile
I hold on to memories I'd like to keep fresh
There's something I'd like to tell you
With words more precious than a goodbye
Unremarkable yet special
See, things that couldn't have been
Seen if it weren't for these eyes
Why? They begin to overflow
So, if I were to be born again
I would surely choose this place once more
So, if we were to meet again
I'd never let you go, I'd choose the present
Even if no promises were made
Even if I'm lost in days of loneliness
Those tears will be alright,
dawn will surely break
I'm whispering our lullaby
for you to come back home
Do you have someone to praise you?
You're traveling to heaven, then?
I'm not sure I understand...
You've got a nice body, old man.
The largest magical city in the
northern lands, Äußerst.
What's a first-class mage?
What is that trinket?
It means we're elves.
It's the winters of the northern lands.